

SERGEY PRIMAKOVICH

FRONT-END DEVELOPER











CONTACT

Location: Minsk, Belarus

Tel: +37529 6615729

Email: prima.psa@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I'm a developer with experience in building applications using React, Redux, TypeScript or JavaScript. I have experience in back-end development, testing and debugging. I am constantly improving my skills in current technology stack and plan to expand them with new framework like View. In my free time I usually solve tasks on Codewars, read technical literature (K.Simpson, A. Bhargava) and improve my English level. I'm open to your suggestions.

SKILLS

- React
- CSS/SCSS
- Redux
- Redux-Thunk
- JavaScript
- Redux-Toolkit
- TypeScript
 GIT
- Python
- Unit test
- Django
- Storybook
- HTMI
- Axios

LANGUAGES

English: B1 (in progress)

Russian: native

WORK EXPERIENCE

PROJECTS AS FRONT-END DEVELOPER (part-time)

2022 - present

• T4U TICKETS

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, RTK, Mantine, Axios, React-Router-Dom, Yup

JOBORED

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Thunk, Mantine, Axios, React-Router-Dom

PLANNER

Stack: React, Redux, Typescript, Thunk, MUI, Axios

T4U BACK

Stack: Python, Django, Rest-framework

Digital Marketing	Entrepreneur	2017 -	2022

2017 - 2017 **CTR Company**

PHP Developer

Studio IT 2013 - 2016

PHP Developer

Belarusian Printing House 2011 - 2013

IT automation department

Systems Engineer

EDUCATION

IT INCUBATOR 2023

Front-end developer

(React, Redux. Typescript, Thunk, RTK)

RS SCHOOL 2022

Front-end developer

(JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Preprocessors, GIT,

DOM, Events, Node.js)

POLYGLOT ENGLISH SCHOOL 2019

Completed language courses A1, A2

BSUIR 2006 - 2011

Systems Engineer